Guide to the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture records, 1954-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Photographs, circa 1960-1969 (Box 53)
  - Building Parts, 223-228 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 229-234 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 235-240 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 241-243 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 244-246 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 247-249 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 250-252 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 253-255 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 256-258 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 259-263 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 264-268 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 269-274 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 275-280 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 281, 284-286 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 282, 283, 287, 288, 291 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 290, 292 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 293-297 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 298-301 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 302-304 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 305-307 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 308-311 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 312-315 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 317-321 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 322-326 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 327-332 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 333-338 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 339-342 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 343-346 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 345-350 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 352-356 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 357-362 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 367-369 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 370, 374, 376, 377, 380 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 371, 372 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 373, 375, 378 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 381 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 383, 386-388 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 389-394 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 395-400 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 401-405 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 406-409 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 410-413 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 414-416 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 417-419 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, 420-422 (Box 36)
  - Building Parts, unnumbered (1 of 9) (Box 37)
  - Building Parts, unnumbered (2 of 9) (Box 37)
  - Building Parts, unnumbered (3 of 9) (Box 37)
  - Building Parts, unnumbered (4 of 9) (Box 37)
  - Building Parts, unnumbered (5 of 9) (Box 37)
  - Building Parts, unnumbered (6 of 9) (Box 37)
  - Building Parts, unnumbered (7 of 9) (Box 37)
  - Building Parts, unnumbered (8 of 9) (Box 37)
  - Building Parts, unnumbered (9 of 9) (Box 37)
  - Cabinets (display), closed cabinets (1 of 2) (Box 37)
  - Cabinets (display), closed cabinets (2 of 2) (Box 37)
  - Carved panels, doors (1 of 4) (Box 37)
  - Carved panels, doors (2 of 4) (Box 37)
  - Carved panels, doors (3 of 4) (Box 37)
  - Carved panels, doors (4 of 4) (Box 37)
  - Carved wooden figures, figurines (1 of 5) (Box 37)
  - Carved wooden figures, figurines (2 of 5) (Box 37)
  - Carved wooden figures, figurines (3 of 5) (Box 37)
  - Carved wooden figures, figurines (4 of 5) (Box 37)
  - Carved wooden figures, figurines (5 of 5) (Box 37)
  - Chairs (Box 37)
  - Manuscripts (1 of 3) (Box 37)
  - Manuscripts (2 of 3) (Box 37)
  - Manuscripts (3 of 3) (Box 37)
  - Minaret-shaped objects (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous Objects (1 of 3) (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous Objects (2 of 3) (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous Objects (3 of 3) (Box 37)
  - Muscial Instruments (Box 37)
  - Parts for Priest Houses (1 of 7) (Box 37)
  - Parts for Priest Houses (2 of 7) (Box 37)
  - Parts for Priest Houses (3 of 7) (Box 37)
  - Parts for Priest Houses (4 of 7) (Box 37)
  - Parts for Priest Houses (5 of 7) (Box 37)
  - Parts for Priest Houses (6 of 7) (Box 37)
  - Parts for Priest Houses (7 of 7) (Box 37)
  - Spears, Swords, Paddles, Knives (1 of 2) (Box 37)
  - Spears, Swords, Paddles, Knives (2 of 2) (Box 37)
  - Statues (Buddhas/Religious Figures) (1 of 5) (Box 37)
  - Statues (Buddhas/Religious Figures) (2 of 5) (Box 37)
  - Statues (Buddhas/Religious Figures) (3 of 5) (Box 37)
  - Statues (Buddhas/Religious Figures) (4 of 5) (Box 37)
  - Statues (Buddhas/Religious Figures) (5 of 5) (Box 37)
  - Tables, Benches, Screens (1 of 4) (Box 37)
  - Tables, Benches, Screens (2 of 4) (Box 37)
  - Tables, Benches, Screens (3 of 4) (Box 38)
  - Tables, Benches, Screens (4 of 4) (Box 38)
  - Thai Silk Fabrics (1 of 2) (Box 38)
  - Thai Silk Fabrics (2 of 2) (Box 38)
  - Tapestries (1 of 8) (Box 38)
  - Tapestries (2 of 8) (Box 38)
  - Tapestries (3 of 8) (Box 38)
  - Tapestries (4 of 8) (Box 38)
  - Tapestries (5 of 8) (Box 38)
  - Tapestries (6 of 8) (Box 38)
  - Tapestries (7 of 8) (Box 38)
  - Tapestries (8 of 8) (Box 38)
  - Theatre Masks, Headpieces (puppets) (1 of 2) (Box 38)
  - Theatre Masks, Headpieces (puppets) (2 of 2) (Box 38)
- Architectural Records, 1954, circa 1960-1969 and undated (Box 38)
  The architectural records in this collection document the various drawings of the proposed Thai Village site and plans for the various buildings that were to be constructed. Records include those from Louis Pursel, of Louis Pursel and Associates, whose role in the project included the siting of the Thai buildings, the possible design of additional buildings, grading, drainage, and plans for utilities, the architectural firm of Wong and Wong and the engineering firm of Towill Corporation. The Foundation also commissioned Professor Plue Chankao, Professor of Architecture for the Fine Arts University, Bangkok, to draw up the plans for the Royal Pantheon and the Wat Phra Kaeo. The records are primarily diazo, but also include ink, pencil, and pastels. Of particular interest are Louis Pursel's original sketches of the Thai House in color pencil and pencil on diazo.
  Digital use copies exist for some of the architectural records and have been identified below. Digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access please contact a reference archivist prior to visiting the library.
  - Lou Pursel's Sketches of Thai Houses. Louis Pursel, architect. undated. Color pencil and pencil on diazo. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Floor Plan of Concrete Foundation, 1 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Sep 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D7F7, Box 31)
  - Plan to Show the Connection of Pavilon Wooden Posts with Secon (B) Concrete Foundation, 2 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Sep 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D7F7, Box 31)
  - Wooden Floor Plan of Exactly Replica from Royal Dusit Palace, Golden Pavilion, 3 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Sep 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D7F7, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation of Exactly [sic] Replica from Royal Dusit Palace, Golden Pavilion, 4 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Sep 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D7F7, Box 31)
  - Side Elevation of Exactly [sic] Replica from Royal Dusit Palace, Golden Pavilion, 5 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Sep 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D7F7, Box 31)
  - Cross Section Front Elevation, 6 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Sep 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D7F7, Box 31)
  - Cross Section of Side Elevation, 7 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Sep 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D7F7, Box 31)
  - Ceiling Plan of Golden Pavilion, 8 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Sep 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D7F7, Box 31)
  - Cross Section of Concrete Foundation, 9 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Sep 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D7F7, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation of Concrete - Foundation A, 10 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Sep 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D7F7, Box 31)
  - Floor Plan, Plan Column, dwg 1/3. [Circa 1962]. Diazo, pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F1, Box 31)
  - Side Elevation, Front Elevation. [Pursel, Louis, architect]. [Circa 1962]. Diazo, pencil, photocopy, sepia diazo, vellum. (Opaperfolder C1D9F1, Box 31)
  - [Cross Sections A & B], dwg 3/3. [Circa 1962]. Pencil, photocopy. (Opaperfolder C1D9F1, Box 31)
    Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
  - Section A-A, Section B-B, plan: common rafter, purlin, plan: column purlin, purlin, ridge, plan: eave board, gable, principle rafter, brace strut. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. [Circa 1963]. Diazo, ink. (Opaperfolder C1D9F2, Box 31)
  - Plan: Column Section at Ground Floor, Plan: Door Panel, Plan: Panel Height, Plan: Floor Plank, Plan: Floor Joist, Plan: Wood Beam, [Siamese House at Ayuthya]. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. [Circa 1963]. Diazo, ink. (Opaperfolder C1D9F2, Box 31)
  - Long Section, Cross Section, Plan: Column Purlin, Purlin, Ridge, Plan: Gable, Kingpost, Tie Beam, Principle Rafter, Plan: Eave Board, [Siamese House at Ayudthya].[Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. [Circa 1963]. Diazo, ink. (Opaperfolder C1D9F2, Box 31)
  - Plan: Column Section at Ground Floor, Plan: Window, Door, Column Section at +2.75M, Plan: Wall Plank, Plan: Floor Plank, Plan: Floor Joist, Plan: Beam Hight [sic] +1.80M, [Siamese House at Ayudthya]. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. [Circa 1963]. Diazo, ink. (Opaperfolder C1D9F2, Box 31)
  - Elevation, Plan, Siamese House at Ayuthya. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. [Circa 1963]. Diazo, ink. (Opaperfolder C1D9F2, Box 31)
  - Long Section, Cross Section, Plan: Column Purlin, Purlin, Ridge, Plan: Gable, Kingpost, Tie Beam, Principle Rafter, Plan: Eave Board, [Siamese House at Ayuthya]. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. [Circa 1963]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F2, Box 31)
  - Plan: Column Section at Ground Floor, Plan: Door Panel, Plan: Pakol Panel Height, Plan: Floor Plank, Plan: Floor Joist, Plan: Beam, [Siamese House at Ayuthya]. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. [Circa 1963]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F2, Box 31)
  - Sala Karn Prarian, Plan, Front Elevation, Side Elevation. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. 196[4] Oct 30. Ink. (Opaperfolder C1D9F3, Box 31)
  - Long Section A-A, Cross Section B-B. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. undated.Ink. (Opaperfolder C1D9F3, Box 31)
  - Plan: Principle Rafter, Plan: King Post, Plan: Gable, Plan: Tad. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. undated. Ink. (Opaperfolder C1D9F3, Box 31)
  - Plan: Column (C) Section at Ground Floor, Plan: Wood Rafter, Plan: Purlin, Plan: Ridge, Purlin, Column Purlin, Eave Board. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. undated. Ink. (Opaperfolder C1D9F3, Box 31)
  - Plan, Sketch Plate 2, 1 of 4. Keovimol, S.; Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1963 Jul 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation, Sketch Plate 2, 2 of 4. Keovimol, S.; Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1963 Jul 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Side Elevation, Sketch Plate 2, 3 of 4. Keovimol, S.; Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1963 Jul 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Long Section, Sketch Plate 2, 4 of 4. Keovimol, S.; Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1963 Jul 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation, Sketch Plate 1, 2 of 4. Keovimol, S.; Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1963 Jul 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Floor Plan of Concrete Foundation, 1 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt; stamped by Wong, Howard M. Y. [Circa 1964]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Plan to Show the Connection of Pavilion Wooden Posts with Secon (B) Concrete Foundation, 2 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt; stamped by Wong, Howard M. Y. [Circa 1964]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Wooden, Floor Plan of Exactly Replica from Royal Dusit Palace, Golden Pavilion, 3 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt; stamped by Wong, Howard M. Y. [Circa 1964]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation of Exactly Replica from Royal Dusit Palace, Golden Pavilion, 4 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt; stamped by Wong, Howard M. Y. [Circa 1964]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Side Elevation of Exactly [sic] Replica from Royal Dusit Palace, Golden Pavilion, 5 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt; stamped by Wong, Howard M. Y. [Circa 1964]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Cross Section Front Elevation, 6 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt; stamped by Wong, Howard M. Y. [Circa 1964]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Cross Section of Side Elevation, 7 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt; stamped by Wong, Howard M. Y. 1964 Aug 20. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Ceiling Plan of Golden Pavilion, 8 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt; stamped by Wong, Howard M. Y. [Circa 1964]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Cross Sec[tion of Concrete Foundation], 9 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt; stamped by Wong, Howard M. Y. [Circa 1964]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation of Concrete Foundation, 10 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt; stamped by Wong, Howard M. Y. [Circa 1964]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F4, Box 31)
  - Proposed Site Plan of Southeast Asian Cultural Center, Kahana Valley, Oahu. Louis Pursel, architect. 1966 Sep. Pencil, diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F5, Box 31)
  - Land Use District Boundaries: United States Department of the Interior Geological Survey, Kahana Quadrangle, Hawaii -- City and County of Honolulu, Island of Oahu. United States Department of the Interior Geological Survey; State of Hawaii Land Use Commission. 1963 Aug 23. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F5, Box 31)
  - United States Department of the Interior Geological Survey, Kahana Quadrangle, Hawaii -- City and County of Honolulu, Island of Oahu. United States Department of the Interior Geological Survey. 1954. Color print. (Opaperfolder C1D9F5, Box 31)
  - [Topographical Land Survey, Kahana Area, Hawaii]. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F5, Box 31)
  - [Topographical Land Survey of Proposed Village Site, Hawaii]. Undated. Diazo with ink, pencil with colored pencil, pastels. (Opaperfolder C1D9F5, Box 31)
  - Small 1st Rough Study [Proposed Village Site, Hawaii]. [Louis Pursel, architect]. Undated. Pencil with colored pencil, diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F6, Box 31)
  - [Proposed Village Site, Hawaii]. [Louis Pursel, architect]. Undated. Pencil with colored pencil, pastels. (Opaperfolder C1D9F6, Box 31)
  - [Proposed Village Site alternative version, Hawaii]. [Louis Pursel, architect]. 1966 Aug 26. Diazo, diazo with crayon, diazo with pastels. (Opaperfolder C1D9F6, Box 31)
  - [Proposed Village Site, Hawaii]. [Louis Pursel, architect]. Undated. Diazo with colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F6, Box 31)
  - [Proposed Village Site, Hawaii]. [Louis Pursel, architect]. Undated. Diazo with colored pencil and topographical details. (Opaperfolder C1D9F6, Box 31)
  - [Topographical Land Survey of Proposed Village Site Version 1, Hawaii]. [Louis Pursel, architect]. Undated. Diazo with colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F6, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation (Scheme "B"). Louis Pursel, architect. 1962 Jul. Pen. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - Side Elevation (Scheme "B"). Louis Pursel, architect. 1962 Jul. Pen. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - Floor Plan (Scheme "B"). Louis Pursel, architect. 1962 Jul. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation (Scheme "A"). Louis Pursel, architect. 1962 Jul. Ink. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation. Louis Pursel, architect. [Circa 1962]. Diazo with colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - Side Elevation. Louis Pursel, architect. [Circa 1962]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - Section. Louis Pursel, architect. [Circa 1962]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - Floor Plan. Louis Pursel, architect. [Circa 1962]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation, Side Elevation. [Panya-ngarm, Somchai]. Diazo, pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - Proposed Office Layout. Undated. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - Plan of Existing Office. Undated. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F7, Box 31)
  - [Sketch of Proposed Thai Village]. Undated. Pencil and colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F8, Box 31)
  - Schematic Study for Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture. Louis Pursel, architect. [Circa 1961-1966]. Pencil and colored pencil, diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F8, Box 31)
  - Beach and Lower State Park. [Donald Wolbrink and Associates]. [1966]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F8, Box 31)
  - [Proposed Thai Village]. Louis Pursel, architect. [Circa 1961-1966]. Watercolor. (Opaperfolder C1D9F8, Box 31)
  - [Proposed Thai Village]. [Louis Pursel, architect]. [Circa 1961-1966]. Black diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F8, Box 31)
  - [Proposed Thai Village]. Louis Pursel & Associates. [Circa 1961-1966]. Colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F8, Box 31)
  - [Proposed Thai Village]. Louis Pursel & Associates. [Circa 1961-1966]. Black diazo, colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C1D9F8, Box 31)
  - [Sketch of Coastal Area and Thai Village]. Undated. Pencil and pastels (on tracing paper). (Opaperfolder C1D9F8, Box 31)
  - [Sketch of Proposed Thai Village]. Undated. Pencil and pastels. (Opaperfolder C1D9F8, Box 31)
  - [Sketch of Playing Fields]. Undated. Marker. (Opaperfolder C1D9F8, Box 31)
  - Kahana Valley State Park, Parcel 3, Tax Map: 5-2-02-12, C.S.F. No. 14821. Survey Division, Department of Accounting and General Services, State of Hawaii. 1966 Feb 9. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - Kahana Valley State Park, Parcels 4, 5, 6, 7 and 8, Tax Map5-2-02, C.S.F. No. 14822 to 14825. Survey Division, Department of Accounting and General Services, State of Hawaii. 1966 Feb 9. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - Kahana Valley State Park, Parcels 10 to 18 (inclusive), Tax Map 5-2-02, C.S.F. No. 14826 to 14827. Survey Division, Department of Accounting and General Services, State of Hawaii. 1966 Feb 9. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - Kahana Valley State Park, Parcels 19, 20 and 21 (inclusive), Tax Map 5-2-02, C.S.F. No. 14828, 14829 and 14830. Survey Division, Department of Accounting and General Services, State of Hawaii. 1966 Feb 9. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - Kahana Valley State Park, Parcels 50, 51, 52, 53 and 54, Tax Map 5-2-03 and 06, C.S.F. No. 14837, 14838 and 14839. Survey Division, Department of Accounting and General Services, State of Hawaii. 1966 Feb 9. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - Kahana Valley State Park, Parcels 56, 58, 59 and 60, Tax Map 5-2-03, 05 and 06, C.S.F. no. 14840, 14841, 14842, and 14843. Survey Division, Department of Accounting and General Services, State of Hawaii. 1966 Feb 9. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - Kahana Valley State Park, Parcels 22 to 28 (inclusive), 30 to 43 (inclusive), 45 to 49 (inclusive), 55 and 62 to 66 (inclusive), Tax Map 5-2-05 and 06, C.S.F. No. 14831 to 14836. Survey Division, Department of Accounting and General Services, State of Hawaii. 1966 Feb 9. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - State Park Development, Kaneohe. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - Public Use Str[ip], Kahuku. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - [Photograph Kahana Valley Peninsula]. Undated. Photograph. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - Thai Village Study, [1960s] Aug 26. Pencil, colored pencil, blueprint. (Opaperfolder C1D9F9, Box 31)
  - Thai Pavilion, Floor Plan, Plate No. 1. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Sep 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC1, Box 31)
  - Thai Pavilion, Front Elevation, Plate No. 2. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Nov 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC1, Box 31)
  - Thai Pavilion, Side Elevation, Plate No. 3. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Feb 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC1, Box 31)
  - Thai Pavilion, Cross Section A-A, Plate No. 4. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Feb 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC1, Box 31)
  - Thai Pavilion, Long Section B-B, Plate No. 5. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Feb 19. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC1, Box 31)
  - Thai Pavilion, Elevation Showed the Level, Plate No. 6. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Feb 20. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC1, Box 31)
  - Thai Pavilion, Elevation Showed the Level, Plate No. 7. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Feb 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC1, Box 31)
  - Phatreplilok Building, Elevation Drawing, Drawing of Section A-2 & B-2 (includes letter from Sawasdi and colored photographs showing various sections of Phatreplilok building). Plue Chankeo. 1965 Jul 27. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC2, Box 31)
  - Phatreplilok Building, Floor Plan, Elevation Plan, Ceiling Plan, Cross Section A, Cross Section B, Plan of Upper Part (includes letter from Sawasdi and 1 Black and White photograph of Phatreplilok Building). Plue Chankeo. 1965 Sep 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC2, Box 31)
  - Phatreplilok Building, Exact Replica - floor plan drawing, Exact Replica - elevation plan drawing (includes letters from Sawasdi). Plue Chankeo. 1965 Apr 29. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC2, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, Plan, 1 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Nov 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, [Front Elevation], 2 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Nov 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, Section, 3 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Feb 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, Long Section of the 4th Roof and Section of the Top Roof, Plan at Section A-A, 4 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, Cross Section of 4th Roof, 5 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, Cross Section and Long Section of 3rd Roof, 6 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, Cross Section and Long Section of 2nd Roof, 7 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, Cross Section of 1st Roof, 8 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, Long Section of 1st Roof at Back and Side Elevation and at Front Elevation or Main Entrance, 9 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, Plan of 2nd Step Ceiling at Centre of the Hall, 10 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, Plan of 3rd Step Ceiling at Centre of the Hall, 11 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, R.C. Roof Construction at I, 12 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, R.C. Roof Construction at H, 13 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, R.C. Roof Construction at G, 14 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, R.C. Roof Construction at F, 15 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, R.C. Roof Construction at E, 16 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, R.C. Roof Construction at D, 17 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, R.C. Roof Construction at C, 18 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Palace, R.C. Roof Construction at B, 19 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)